<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="calculatorButtonString">Guaranteed wage calculator</string>
    <string name="monthlyButtoString">Monthly wage</string>
    <string name="faqButtonString">Frequently asked questions</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="calculateButton">Calculate</string>
    <string name="goBackButtonDescription">Go back</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="labelWhereWork">Where in the country do you drive? City or place:</string>
    <string name="descInfoKollektiv">Information about collective agreement</string>
    <string name="descWhereWork">Information about place</string>
    <string name="hintWhereWorkTextField">e.g. Malmö</string>
    <string name="hintHoursTextField">e.g. 174</string>
    <string name="labelHours">How many hours have you worked?</string>
    <string name="labelKollektivavtal">Does the company have a collective agreement?</string>
    <string name="labelHoursToWorkAgreement">Working time measurement:</string>
    <string name="placeHolderPercentage">100%</string>
    <string name="descMonthlySalary">Monthly wage</string>
    <string name="descLogo">Touch 12 times</string>
    <string name="descWorkedHours">Information about worked hours</string>
    <string name="monthlysalary">Monthly wage</string>
    <string name="faq">Frequently asked questions</string>
    <string name="closeButton">Close</string>
    <string name="not_member">Not a member yet?</string>
    <string name="workAllWeekDays">Are you scheduled for all the days of the week?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FaqActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_monthly">MonthlyActivity</string>
    <string name="tv14">You are covered by the collective agreement if your company is a member of the Biltrafikens Arbetsgivareförbund (Swedish Road Transport Employers\' Association) or have signed an agreement directly with Transport. Ask your company or check with your local branch of Transport. Call 010–480 30 00 and state where you work. We will then need your employer\'s organisation number, which is on the receipt that the customer gets.</string>
    <string name="tv16">How is the hourly wage calculated?</string>
    <string name="tv13">How do I know if I am covered by the collective agreement?\"</string>
    <string name="tv12">If you work at a company with a collective agreement and drive for a percentage wage you have the right to a guaranteed wage.</string>
    <string name="tv11">Who is covered by a guaranteed wage?</string>
    <string name="tv17">If you enter all the days of the week into a schedule, the calculated average time that you work during the year as a full time employee is 166.4 hours/month. The parties have agreed upon that time as a calculation basis for calculating hourly wages. If you only work on weekdays (Monday - Friday, holiday-free week) the basis for calculation is 174 hours instead.. Your employment contract must state whether you will work 38.25 or 40 hours a week.</string>
    <string name="tv18">Which drivers have a right to a monthly wage?</string>
    <string name="tv19">"From the 1st December 2017, employers must pay a monthly wage to those drivers who only drive community paid journeys negotiated after that date. For example, service transportation, medical transport and school lifts. The employer may also choose to pay those that drive a mixture of journeys (community paid taxi traffic and other taxi traffic) with a monthly wage according to the collective agreement. "</string>
    <string name="tv21">"If you think that your wage does not correspond to the applicable collective agreement you can calculate your wage using this app.  If it turns out that your wage is not correct you must point this out to your employer. If you have a problem as a member you can contact your local branch of Transport. "</string>
    <string name="tv20">What can I do if my wage is not correct?</string>
    <string name="tv22">What time is calculated as working time?</string>
    <string name="tv23">All working time is counted as working time, that is the time that you are at your employer\'s disposal. Breaks are not working time, they are your own time, and when on a break neither are you at the employer\'s disposal.  It is therefore important that you log out of the system when you take a break. This is so that the calculation of the working time and your wages are correct.</string>
    <string name="tv24">Wage information</string>
    <string name="tv25">"As a driver you have the right to receive a wage statement from your employer. It should also state how much tax has been deducted. The wage statement should also state how many hours you have worked and been absent during the period and paid and unpaid holidays. All payments regulated by the agreement shall be specified, for example unsocial hours payment, overtime etc. If you drive for a percentage wage the driven amount as a basis for the wage must be reported (also via an appendix). As a driver you must acknowledge payment when it is not via bank, postal giro or other secure method. "</string>
    <string name="notEmpty">This field cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="titleLocationInfoDialog">"Where in the country do you drive? "</string>
    <string name="bodyLocationInfoDialog">Enter where you are stationed here.</string>
    <string name="titleWorkedHoursInfoDialog">How many hours have you worked?</string>
    <string name="bodyWorkedHoursInfoDialog">Enter the number of hours here, which you have worked in the calender month that you want to calculate your guaranteed wage for</string>
    <string name="titleCollectiveAgreementInfoDialog">Does the company have a collective agreement?</string>
    <string name="bodyCollectiveAgreementInfoDialog">Guaranteed wage only applies to those who work in a company that has a collective agreement with Transport. If you do not know whether there is a collective agreement where you work, call Transport and check.</string>
    <string name="titlePercentageOfFulltimeInfoDialog">Working time measurement</string>
    <string name="bodyPercentageOfFulltimeInfoDialog">You will find that on your certificate of employment . The working time measurement is the % of full time that you must work</string>
    <string name="bodyWorkAllDaysInfoDialog">If you can be scheduled all the days of the week, then you should choose YES. However, if you only schedule Monday to Friday weekend, choose NO.</string>
    <string name="titleWorkAllDaysInfoDialog">Are you scheduled for all the days of the week?</string>
    <string name="tvResult">Your monthly wage must be at least:</string>
    <string name="tvResultWithVaccation">* Monthly wage + vaccation pay:</string>
    <string name="tvAverageHourlyWage">Average hourly wage:</string>
    <string name="tvVaccationPay">* Vacction pay:</string>
    <string name="tvMonthly1">"From the 1st December 2017, employers must pay a monthly wage to those drivers who only drive community paid journeys negotiated after that date. For example, service transportation, medical transport and school lifts. The employer may also choose to pay those that drive a mixture of journeys (community paid taxi traffic and other taxi traffic) with a monthly wage according to the collective agreement. "</string>
    <string name="hourlyWage1th1664">Hourly wage, 1/166,4 of monthly wage:</string>
    <string name="hourlyWage1th174">Hourly wage, 1/174 of monthly wage:</string>
    <string name="monthlyPayTitle">Monthly wage, at least:</string>
    <string name="bitraden">Co-drivers (employees who sit beside the driver and do not have a taxi driver permit)</string>
    <string name="afterTwoYearsTitle">Wages for drivers after two years in the job</string>
    <string name="startWage">Starting wage for drivers</string>
    <string name="vaccationPayResultInfo">* In cases where holiday pay is paid out at each wage point, it must be at least as much as the stated sum. Otherwise, the pay must be collected and paid out in conjunction with holiday being taken.</string>
    <string name="no_collective_agreement">No collective agreement - No guaranteed wage</string>
</resources>